It's started, Ano channel, applause!
Your mood is a little different from usual, isn't it, Ano?
It's like your body is asking for something that will give you a big shock.
It's like her ideas just keep bubbling out of her like water.
In short, she's a super-hyper-ultra media creator.
You know what I mean?
You're such a super-hyper-ultra media creator.
I've been offered a job.
Well, I'm sure he will.
From Toyota.
As an initiative to support creators
They're distributing video clips and music clips of the popular car IARIS running.
And let creators freely create their own videos.
YARIS Director's Cut" is a project that we're currently working on.
We have already created many wonderful videos.
We have already produced many wonderful video works, and we would like you to promote the fun of video creation.
This time, we got an offer.
A proper one... a proper one... a proper one...
A proper one?
Go!
Wow!
Oh, my God!
Me.
To give us an idea of what we're looking at, let's see some of the video work that the creators have done.
I'm going to do it! Great! When there are no lights, life is not fun!
When there are lights! Yes!
Yaris is the best!
Yaris director's cut.
It's a little hard to see, honestly.
It's kind of amazing, isn't it?
I can't do this.
What's that?
There's a guy in a fish-jacking, and he's distributed with the footage.
Material? Yamaguchi?
Is it free material? Mr. Yamaguchi.
Special.
Special free material? YamaguchiSpecial
I just saw the two films you've made, how did you like them?
I think it's important to have a sense of fun, so freedom, freedom is the first thing.
That's my theme, too.
Could you please prepare the usual clay?
Yes, sir.
I want it to run freely in various worlds.
Not just the real world. I want to express the idea of going to various places.
Do you know what stop motion is? It's a visual technology, or rather, it's a frame-by-frame motion. I want to do something like that.
Hmm? No smoke?
But I've been to driving school.
I've driven before.
I'm really good at it.
I'm not a good driver.
I can't study.
Study...
Good.
I got it.
Yes, sir.
Now that we've done that, we need to create a world to run in.
I've come up with four things in my mind as I'm working on it.
First, I need a road in the city.
The second is a nature area, such as a meadow or a flower garden.
The third is a forest.
The fourth one is something I'm preparing, or I'll tell you later.
Then, in the world where you want to run...
We need a road in the city and a flower garden.
And a forest.
Maybe a few more buildings.
Something like...
Latour style.
Latour?
Some kind of celebrity apartment building.
that celebrities live in.
branded condominiums?
Do you mean a brand name apartment building where celebrities live?
Yes, La Tour La Tour.
What kind of La Tour?
Do you have a reception desk?
This is Latour first.
This is Latour.
It's where all the influencers live.
Like celebrities.
This is a tower apartment.
It's a tower.
It's a tower, so it's more secure.
The rooms are smaller.
That's why it's so thin.
I'm just guessing.
I'm too prejudiced.
Okay, good.
It's nice.
And then there's people.
A few passersby.
People can be distracting if they're not clear.
I'm mainly going to be driving, so this time...
I'm going to use a stick figure.
I see.
Do you have a name for the celebrity? I'll be the main character, so I'll be the stick figure.
Celebrity.
Do you have a name for him? That mob character.
Ayanogo
He's a celebrity.
Okay, next, here in the meadow.
A field of flowers.
Butterflies
I want to put lots of pretty things
I want to drive a car. I want to drive a car.
I don't want to be the one driving, I want to be the car, the form and the look.
Isn't it cool?
You don't seem to know the way.
Directions? Not without a navigation system.
When you take a cab...
"Where do you want to go? They say...?
Yes.
I'm serious.
I'm like, "Shut up.
Are you asking me the truth?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What? What?
I don't know if I'm going down the street.
Like, I don't know.
Is it a street you know?
A street you know?
Uh, Dogenzaka.
Or an intersection.
An intersection?
I know an intersection in Nishi Ward.
There's a good buckwheat noodle shop near the intersection in Nishi Ward.
Sanshoku Kou
It's 3rd class A! Sando Kou
Kamo soba (duck soba) is delicious!
Do you have to drive to get to places like Nishi Ward?
Yes, there is no station in Nishi Ward, so you can't go there by train.
So a car is a must!
I'm here by car.
I don't know what else to do.
I want someone who can drive.
My girlfriend is a must
We often talk about parking
You know what I'm talking about.
You say you like that one.
That makes me laugh.
I laugh at people who dress up like that. It's not that I laugh at them, it's just that I don't like them.
Just say, "This is cool.
I don't think it's cool.
If you said that...
I'd be really touched.
If you don't say that, then I don't know what to do with my time.
I don't know what to do.
I really like your car.
I really want to drive.
It's so cool. It's like the surface of the water.
Then the forest.
The forest is like, "Oh, there's so many animals in the forest.
The intersection at Misk...
That taiyaki shop.
There's the taiyaki shop.
And then, when you turn that corner, there's an orchestre.
I got a bear.
It's blue.
I've been meeting a lot of influencers.
There are a lot of influencers who are friends with celebrities through their work.
I asked them where they meet these celebrities.
I asked them where they meet them.
At a bar around Lively.
I said, "At the bar in Lively.
I was able to do it.
Rabbit.
Cute!
middle of the night
5th all-nighter
The fourth one? Did it come?
Come on back. Here you go.
Hello, sir.
What is it?
Mr. Iguchi from Westland is here.
Please stop it.
It's his teeth.
They showed my teeth so much on that channel.
I've had three dental jobs this week alone.
Isn't that great?
I don't need any more teeth.
But when I saw them before, they were like caves.
You're the only person I've ever heard say that about.
So, let's go to the fourth zone where Yaris runs.
I made it look like he wandered into Mr. Iguchi's mouth.
I have no idea what that means.
Tell me what you're doing.
I'm the one who's doing something.
No, you tell me what you're doing.
I'm going to make it.
Can you open your mouth for me?
Nothing's changed.
You have the ingredients!
You don't have to come all the way down here right now.
Let's see what you've got.
Wow! Wow!
Oh, my God, right in the middle.
It's a real gem!
But I've been talking to Ano about it.
I'm getting to the point where I'm thinking of fixing my teeth too.
Why?
Well, you know, with all the TV shows and stuff...
I've had a lot of contact with dentists.
He said I should get it fixed.
Ignore him.
It's just for her.
Why not?
No, but I'm just doing this.
What are you doing?
I'm driving this time.
What do you mean?
This is how we're going to do it.
That's why we're doing car episodes.
Car episodes.
Interesting car stories.
I do have a driver's license, though.
You do?
It's funny to imagine you in a car.
Of course.
You look like a kid in a car.
Not really.
But Tanaka-san from Bakusho Mondai is my senior at the office.
Mr. Tanaka is smaller than me.
And at that time, Tanaka-san's manager was also under 160 cm.
And then, we were in a car, a big car, and three little adults were coming out of the car together.
I thought that was objectively terrible.
That's funny.
Okay, so it's done.
Bye bye, Mr. Iguchi!
OK, that's enough.
Wait a minute, isn't this really too short?
Both are good, honestly.
It hurts a little more.
Tenshi.
What's that?
I wore an angel ring at the God's movement.
Just like my poochy-waiy-chan character.
Yeah, so keep it on.
I don't like it. I can't move much.
I've already finished with Mr. Iguchi.
I was wondering if you could give me a word of advice
I'd like it if you could write it down for me.
Well, of course.
What are you going to write on the side?
Is that enough? That's the concept of calligraphy.
That's good.
I've got it. - Freedom.
I like it.
I like the way it's written.
It's also about freedom in the sense that it's a Chinese calligraphy on the side.
It's unconventional.
I don't know what I'm doing here, but I don't know what to say.
What kind of calligraphy?
I'm making a commercial.
You can't use your teeth to make a commercial, can you?
It's fine. It's not a commercial, it's sensitive.
Then what was all that about? I got stuck with an iPhone.
I just want to see it. I'm so glad I got to see it.
I took a lot of pictures today to make this film,
I want to put in the footage of the actual Earlis car that's on the website,
But the amount of material is just too much.
So I'm trying to decide how to make it a little more playful, but the amount of material is just too much.
So, I would like to add a little bit of playful decisions in a way that is typical of her.
I wrote the numbers of the video materials on the panel at random earlier,
I'm going to make a piece of work using the images with the numbers on the panel that I pulled out.
I feel like I'm leaving a lot to chance.
This is a game created by the uncertainty of luck.
The process of creation is an art form, and I feel that I have to entertain the audience.
Okay, I'll take care of it right away.
That's too close.
You got it.
Did I hit it?
It looks like a wing attack.
The sign, the picture looks great.
Just because it looks great, doesn't mean it's not great.
This is it.
I'm going to throw them all at once.
Let's do it.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Down.
Melon.
Okay, here's 101.
Now all we have to do is stick these together and we'll be good to go.
Take a picture, please.
Oh, it's so nice to be able to walk through here!
So cute!
No, it's great.
It's great!
It's going to be a good one.
Yes, sir.
Toyota Yaris.
Check out my work on the Director's Cut Project site.
Check out my work!
Subscribe to Ana Channel!
Subscribe!